When I was less .. So it was not good.
It was screens .. broken.
Then when he had nang, then Nang and Timmy trained very much,
That if someone was teased then "go away instead of attacking" and such things.
Then we realized that when he feels he is on and getting so angry, and feels that he is losing control
Then he will "I want to call my mom".
When he said it was a signal, he is getting an outbreak and has no control over those outbreaks.
But when he had to call, the phone got right away and then he had to call me.
Then I talked to him, sometimes I could calm him down so he could continue his day
But then Nang was with him.
Everything was raging there
It is many years of working and struggling and training, it is not just a week.
He does not want to get the outbreaks, does not want to be angry, he wants to feel good simply.
He is the best guy in the world.
He has plenty of humor, my God ...
... so caring.
He is my assistant and my friend.
He is great.
He helps me with a lot at school and how I progressed.
I have been approved on topics when I have Amir and stuff.
So it is really good.
No eruptions, nothing.
Can sit and make ten pages math.